(Bernadette:)Hurry! We're running out of time!
(Sheldon:)- Okay.
- Just do it!
(Sheldon:)Oh, God! One, two, three.
Aah!
(Howard:)Trick or treat, bubbeleh.
(Sheldon:)What?
(Sheldon:)No. You mean this was all a ruse?
Oh, how could I be so stu?...
Damn it, I can't... I can't do this.
(Alice:)Is it my tongue stud?
(Alice:)If that freaks you out,
you're in for a real surprise later.
No, no, no. I can't do this.
(Leonard:)Believe me, I really want to.
- But?
- But I kind of have a girIfriend.
- Are you kidding?
- Uh, you're cool with being friends, right?
Heh. I don't believe this.
(Leonard:)Wait, I don't... Which part?
Heh. I'm so stupid.
I thought for once I'd met a good guy...
(Alice:)- ...but you're just another jackass.
- Oh, no, you have it wrong.